We've arrived at long last at the end of
the course. Um there's only one thing
left to cover for this course and that
is deployment. Um everything you've done
till now has enabled you to build most
anything that you could want. Obviously
there's some other code that you could
do like you could do some backend code
and start talking to databases but that
can be done using pretty much the same
JavaScript you've learned. Um, you could
get into more advanced stuff like React
and that can help you build um, all of
the things that you've been building now
much faster, much easier. Um, and it'll
be much more efficient for users to use.
Um, you could look into all sorts of
various things, but you should be
prepared to do that now with all of the
JavaScript that you've learned. So, the
last thing that we need to do in this
course is teach you how to give it to
someone else. Right now, you can code
just about anything you can dream of,
but it's stuck on your computer. If you
want someone else to access it, you have
to deploy it. So, we're going to talk
about a lot of different ways to deploy.
Um,
and in the next video I will start
talking about how to do that with Gab.